Guide to the Historic Photograph Subject File circa 19th century-20th century
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 20: Pacific Northwest People
  - Carpenters, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Men at Work, 3 items (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Man and horse, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Four people on horse, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Idaho Basque sheepherder, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Northern Pacific land examiners, 1897, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Man in a rocking chair, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Man golfing, 1926, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Men at work, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Prosser- carpentry training, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mr. Gaty, et al- cabinet cards, 7 items (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Men- cabinet cards, 9 items (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Young men- cabinet cards, 7 items (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Young men- portraits, 3 items (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Men- portraits, 3 items (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Men- portraits, 4 items (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Men- cabinet cards, 2 items (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Rev. Drexel and class, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - United Brethren College- class of 1897, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Garfield High School- class of 1905, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified school group, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Parade, c. 1916, 2 items (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Parade, c. 1916, 2 items (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Parade, 2 items (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - "Steptoe Survivors", Umatilla Day 5/4/15, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Hoquiam women send postcard to Hawaiian Queen Lili'uokalani, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - First National Bank, Pullman Employees banquet, Jan. 1908, 1 item (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - State Press Association, excursion of 1893, 2 items (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Postcards, 7 items (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Series 21: People in Groups and Performing Arts
  - Pullman group pictures, boy scouts, et al, 4 items (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Wedding reception, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Family portrait, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Family in motor car, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Family portrait cabinet cards, 4 items (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Family portraits- Portland pioneer family, 1880s, et al, 3 items (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Family portraits, 7 items (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Family portrait c. 1900- negatives included, 4 items (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Family portraits, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Family portraits, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Japanese in Oregon, 1924, 3 items (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Family portrait- three generations, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Colfax Knights of Pythias - night meeting on Steptoe Butte, 1915, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 12.4)
  - Groups on steps of English's Collegiate Academy, Colfax, WA. 1918 and 1922, 8 items (Box 28, Folder 12.5)
  - Colfax band (1910s), 1 item (Box 28, Folder 12.8)
  - "The Alchemist"- Colfax, WA c. 1900, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Annie Oakley play?, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Dance performers, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - High school play, 1898, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Music group, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Waitsburg, WA band, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified portraits, 4 items (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Spokane County Assessors, ca. 1930s-1940s, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 19.5)
  - Calendar (1905) with Spokane landscapes, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - A game of billiards, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Baby christening, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Bullet holes in rear car windshield, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Dinner at "Jimmy Kelley's"- New York, NY, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - European scenes, 9 items (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Human bone pile, Cuba, 1890s, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 25.5)
  - Military in midwest US, early 1900s (gift of Robert Sandberg), 5 items (Box 28, Folder 25.6)
  - Germany military, 1919, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 25.6)
- Series 22: Photographic Artifacts / Portraits
  - Cabinet cards, 4 items (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Cabinet cards, 4 items (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Large cabinet cards- landscapes, 2 items (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Cartes de visite- some identified, 20 items (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Cartes de visite- some identified, 13 items (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Cartes de visite- children, 13 items (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Cartes de visite- some identified, 9 items (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Colton, WA pioneers, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Mjr. Walter Reed- lantern slide -!FRAGILE!-, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - American poets- Whittier, Lavell, Longfellow, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Ambrotype- child, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Stereolithograph cards various dates. See PC 151 for stereographic photos., 4 items (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Alma voice card (cats), 1 item (Box 29, Folder 4.5)
  - Aluminum base photo, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Tintype photo, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Tintype photo, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tintype photos, 3 items (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Tintype photos c. 1928, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Halftone lithographic plate and clipping, 1937, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 9.5)
  - Capt. O.C. Applegate and Joaquin Miller, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Alfred Babb and wife, 3 items (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Eli Babb and family portrait, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Frank S. Baker, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Helen Fickle Baker, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Barbour, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Roy Batty and Clarence Lance, May 1962, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Mrs. E. N. Beach- Palouse, WA pioneer, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - "Steptoe Survivors"- Thomas Beal, Mjr. Kinney, and John Rohn, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Jacob Bellinger, 3 items (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Samuel Benn, 1932, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Muriel Mae Blackmore, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Stewart Bledsoe, 1946, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Anna Roosevelt and John Boettinger, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Marjorie Clay Boye, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - William Compton Brown, Feb, 15, 1959, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Robert O. Bullis, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 25.5)
  - Caroline McGilvra Burke, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Thomas Burke, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Grant Caugh, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - George Rogers Clark, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - John Comstock, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - "Cougar Gus", 1926, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Cumming's family- Lottie, Gideon, John, Abner, and Amos, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - T. S. Eliot, Virginia Woolf, and Vivienne Eliot, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Curly Jim- Spokane Indian c. 1900-1910, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Gen. George Custer and Grand Duke Alexis of Russia, 1872, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Gen. George Custer's quarters, 1875, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - E. D. Albert at villa in Werden, Germany, 1929, 3 items (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Homer and Tim Davenport w. Francis Malheur, and Fred Lockley, c. 1853, 2 items (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Jennie Day, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Senator C. C. Dill, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - George Dodds, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - James Doran, 1944, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Clifford Merrill Drury, Feb 1, 1942, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - R. O. Dunbar, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - W. M. Duncan- Whitman Co. Treasurer Candidate, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - E. C. Elliot - President Purdue Univ., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - John Enos, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Daniel Evans- WA Governor, 1967, 1 item (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Senator A. J. Fariss, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Gov. Elisha P. Ferry, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Otelia Fetting, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Bert Fisher, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - M. Foster, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - James A. Garfield family, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Nellie Garrick, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - George Goode, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William H. Gray and Mrs. Mary A. Dix Gray, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Belle, Allen, and Elizabeth Green, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Elsie and Gertrude Greenwood, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - William Greenwood, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Porter Griswold, 5 items (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Laurel Hagerson-Lemmon, S.D., 1910, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Oliver R. Hall, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Georgia Hams and Georgia Anderson, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Rev. Joseph A. Hanna and wife, 4 items (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Gary Hart, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Louis Hart (governor), 1 item (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Pres. Raymond Hawk, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Gov. Marion Hay, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Mrs. W. G. M. Hays and Crayton Hays, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Sandy Henderson, Larry Sherman, and Edna Night, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Ella Heuneck and husband, Orpha Heuneck, 3 items (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Augustus High, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Samuel Hill, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Stewart Holbrook, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Jack Holch, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Raymond D. Holmes, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Mjr. General O. O. Howard, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Judge John P. Hoyt, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Eva Irby, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Irene Ironhoops, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Capt. Robert L. Irwin, 6 items (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - John Kammerzell, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Roma Kerby, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Fred L. Kilborne, 6 items (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Ollie Kurzer and Myra Fuller, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - David Laidlaw, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Pullman nursery, Edwin F. Landerholm and Max Hinrichs, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - William Horner Latter, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Father Leary, Gonzaga U. (negative), 1 item (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Judge Charles H. Leary, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Robert E. Lee- Richmond, VA April, 1865, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Ruggiero Leoncavallo, 1899, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Abraham Lincoln and funeral procession, 6 items (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Ernest Lister, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Hattie Harris Little, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - A.G. Lloyd, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Elcaine Longmire and wife, Leonard and James Longmire, 4 items (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Magnuson, Warren Senator (Youthful), 1 (oversize) item (Box 30, Folder 50.5)
  - Gen. G.B. McClellan and wife, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Duncan McDonald (with negatives), 4 items (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - John Jay McGilvra and E.M. McGilvra, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Clarissa McKenny, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Bessie and Harry McKenny and Bob and Roy McKenny, 3 items (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Dr. Edwin D. McKenny and wife, Josepha Lott McKenny and residences, 6 items (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Liza McKenny and Louise and Nellie McKenny, 2 items (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Dr. John McLaughlin, 5 items (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Richard McWhorter, 1942, 1 item (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - May Malone and Ollie Kurzer, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Clarence D. Martin- Jan. 13, 1937, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Clarence D. Martin and E.O. Holland, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Clarence D. Martin and family, 7 items (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Clarence D. Martin, 4 items (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Clarence D. Martin, 8 items (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Gov. Martin and group at Mt. Baker Aug. 1933, 2 items (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Clarence D. Martin public appearances, 10 items (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Ezra Meeker, 2 items (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Ezra Meeker, historical postcards, 29 items (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - James B. Metcalfe, c. 1895, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mjr. Gen. Nelson A. Miles, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Mrs. Blanche Funk Miller, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William Minturn, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - D.K. Montreth, Margaret, Thomas, and Walter Montreth, 4 items (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Miles Conway Moore, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Thornton McElroy, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Senator Justin Smith Morrill, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - John Mullan, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Edward R. Murrow, 2 items (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Thomas William Musgrove c. 1891/1892, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Rollin L. Nichols, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Oliphant, 1 item (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Waverly Old, 2 items (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Ethel Olson, 2 items (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Josiah and Nancy Anna Osborne, 3 items (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Jimmy Oswald, 1887, 3 items (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Clyde Pangborn, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Colonel W.R. Parnell, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Harless H. Peck, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - David Perry, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Charles Pickard, 1950, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Simon Plomondon, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Louie Pohl c. 1882, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Eva Poland, ca. 1910s, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 7.5)
  - Frank Truman Post, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - H.J. Quillian, manager of KIRO, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Ed Raboin, Nez Perce translator, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - C.A. Ratcliff, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Col. J.C. Reaines, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rev. S. Reuben Spaulding, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - L. M. Ringer, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Thomas Emerson Ripley, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - John Roberts, Shoshone Indian Mission, Wind River, WY, 1936, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Wallace Wade Robertson, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - John Rogers, governor, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Eleanor and Franklin D. Roosevelt and Gov. Clarence Martin, 3 items (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - C.H. Ross, Puyallup pioneer, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - George William Russell, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Lady Margaret Sackville, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Mary A. Scoggins Gilbanks, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 22.1)
  - Sebenshaller baby, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Frank L. Sefrit, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Gov. Eugene Semple, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Thomas Seymour, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - W.T. Sherman et al, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Ezekiel Allen Shirley, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Sir Sacheverell Sitwell, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Dino Sivo, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Bill Smith, Herman Logan, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - George Snipes, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - John Wilson Snook, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Opal Sperry, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Frank R. Spaulding, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Isaac I. Stevens, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Carrie Strait Fouler, et al, 4 items (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Mjr. Gen. Samuel D. Sturgis, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Gladys Sutton; Laurel, Henry, and Pear Miller, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - James G. Swan, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Kryn Taconis, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Earl Taylor and wife, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Laura Taylor, Otelia Fetting, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Sayde Thompson, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Elizabeth Catherine Allen Thorpe, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Laura Ella Thorpe, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - John J. Tigert, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Harry Tracy, 9 items (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Harry S. Truman, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Judge George Turner, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Dr. N. J. Vavilov, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Francis Vigo, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Henry Villard, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - S.T. Walker, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Matilda Jackson Ware, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Feliz Warren and sister Mary Warren Spaulding, 3 items (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Nancy Van Waters, 1945, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Samuel Weeks, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Carey R. Wilkes, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - James Marshal Wright family, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Yelm Jim, 2 items (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - W.Z. York, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Zoe Zimmerman, 1 item (Box 32, Folder 62)
- Series 23: Transportation
  - Annie Faxon wreck on the Snake R., 1893, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Steamship H.F. Alexander, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Mike Maru- historic steamship, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Gerome- first steamboat on the Columbia R., 1 item (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Steamer Olympian, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Steamer Seattle at Taku glacier, 8/5/08, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Steamer Almota, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Steamship, 1897, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Steamship President Jefferson, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Steamer Lewiston, 1923, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Steamers Flyer, Norma, Chelan, Spokane, and Imnaha, 6 items (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Steamer Coeur D'Alene, 3 items (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Steamer Ione, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Steamer Spokane, 2 items (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Steamer Spokane, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Steamer Spokane, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - S.S. Skagit Chief, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Steamer Lewiston, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Paddle Wheel George Oakes, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - J.M. Hannaford- Mississippi-type riverboat, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Coast Guard patrol boat, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Coast Guard lifeboat, 1935, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Coast Guard picket boat, 1935, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Coast Guard cutter: The Northland, 2 items (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Coast Guard Cutter: Haida, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Coast Guard Cutter: The Tallapoosa, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Coast Guard self bailing motor surf boat, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - U.S. battle fleet in Elliott Bay, 3 items (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - The Atlantic fleet passing the Columbia R., 1 item (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - U.S.S Constitution: "Old Ironsides", 2 items (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - U.S. cruiser Minneapolis, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - U.S.S. Lexington aircraft carrier, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - U.S.S. Lexington, bow, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - U.S. battleship on Puget Sound, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - U.S.S. Medusa, repairship at Bremerton, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - U.S.S. Rixey, San Francisco Bay, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Battleships, and other WW2 ships. Postcards., 11 items (Box 33, Folder 36.5)
  - State room in S.S. Brazil, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Victory ship, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Liberty ship, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - 'Speedway' mail boat on Lake Chelan, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - M.S. Klickitat- tanker, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Tanker, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Duquesne- tanker, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - S.S. Mission Purisima, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - S.S. Edward Nickels, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Poinsett, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Anadarho Victory, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Cargo ship: Kathleen S. Holmes, 2 items (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - The President McKinley, passenger and freight ship, 1 item (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - S.S. America, 2 items (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - The Santa Barbara, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Delbrasil- passenger and cargo ship, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Standby fire pump of Hannibal Victory, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Penawawa Ferry, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Columbia River ferry, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Lyons Ferry, 1956, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Wawawai Ferry, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ferry "Chippewa", 2 items (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Ferry "Enetai", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 8.5)
  - Ferry "Kalakala", 5 items (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Ferry "Commander", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified ferry, probably Snake River, ca. 1922, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 10.5)
  - Diablo Lake excursion boat "Alice Ross", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Cruiser on Lake Chelan, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Schooner "C. S. Holmes", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Three-mast "La Esconcesa", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Windjammers off Port Townsend, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Sailing ship "Commodore", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Sailing ship "Commodore", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Sailing vessels at Port Townsend, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Ship "St. Paul", historic three-master, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Pleasure boats on Puget Sound, 3 items (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Sailing vessels, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - "M. S. Catalyst", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Launching the "Ethel G", 1939, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Seattle fishing boats, 4 items (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Fishing fleet in Seattle, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Fishing boats in Seattle, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Government Locks, Seattle, WA, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 26.1)
  - Willapa harbor, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Ship in harbor, Tacoma area, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Seattle waterfront, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Harbor Island dock, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Schooner "Vigilant", 1 item (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Drill barge at Wawawai, 1962, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - C.P.R. Princess Patricia, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 32.1)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - First school bus (a donkey), Omak, WA 1903, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Twenty-mule teams, Harrington, 1926, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Oregon Trail wagon- Terre Haute, Indiana, 1910, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Old Newport school wagon, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Wagon road out of Yakima Canyon, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - The "Boston Hooihut" over Naches Pass, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Horse and buggy rigs, 11 item (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Horse and buggy rigs, 3 items (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Freight scene- Riverside, WA, 1905; Reserv. excavation w. steam shovel and wagons, 1926, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Freight scenes w. wagon trains, 3 items (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Wagon trains: Bend, Or and Deschutes Co., OR, 3 items (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Gravity-horse railroad car, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Baker fire team, 3 items (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Immigrant train of "Prairie Schooners" - reproduced print, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - "On a tour from Pullman", 1893, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Early transportation to Garfield public schools- horse and wagons, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Horse pulled plow and wagons, 2 items (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Horse drawn water wagon- Sunnyside, WA 1916, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Jacksonville Stage Line, OR, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 51.1)
  - Freighting scene- Crook Co., OR, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Henry Kennedy and horse team near Bend, OR 1912, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Tramway connecting wheat fields to warehouse on Snake R., 1 item (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Tramway at Tramway, ID, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Site of Old Interior Tram below Wawawai, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Early automobile, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Omak, WA school buses, 1932, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Washington motor coach system, 1933, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Snoqualmie Pass- east side, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous automobiles, 7 items (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Early automobiles, 4 items (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - A scenic drive in an automobile, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Oregon Coast Highway, 36 items (Box 34, Folder 63.1)
  - Cody Road to Yellowstone Park, 7 items (Box 34, Folder 63.2)
  - Golden Gate Railway to Yellowstone Park, 1 item (Box 34, Folder 63.3)
  - Palouse Highway, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Washington Roads, 4 items (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Road construction south of Spokane, 1924, 4 items (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Lewiston grade, 1931, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Lewiston Grade, Lewiston, ID, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4.1)
  - Road south of Wenatchee, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Road west of Vantage Ferry, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Road east of Odessa, 1928, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 7)